=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 20=
= طبيبي الخيالي = = الحلقة 20 =
Snake!
ثعبان!
Where?
أين؟
Would you like to have a look?
هل ترغب في إلقاء نظرة؟
I'm not interested.
أنا لست مهتم
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Good for both of you.
جيد لكلاكما.
You guys get to have fun in the mountain,
أنتم يا رفاق تحصلون على المتعة في الجبل ،
while I'm here alone.
بينما أنا هنا لوحدي.
What's the point of staying here?
ما فائدة البقاء هنا؟
There are no customers anyway.
لا يوجد عملاء على أي حال.
Badou.
badou
Nianzhou.
نيانتشو.
Where is your sister?
اين اختك؟
Here.
هنا.
When did they
عندما فعلوا
become so close?
تصبح قريبة جدا؟
That's only natural.
هذا طبيعي فقط.
They stick together every day.
يلتصقون ببعضهم البعض كل يوم.
They are
هم انهم
inseparable.
لا ينفصل.
They just
انهم فقط
didn't sleep together.
لم يناموا معا.
What are they doing there?
ماذا يفعلون هناك؟
They went up the mountain
صعدوا الجبل
to find...
لايجاد...
Badou.
badou
Dry the herbs.
جفف الأعشاب.
Mr. Tang.
السيد.  تانغ.
What are you doing here again?
ماذا تفعل هنا مرة أخرى؟
I just want to know
انا فقط اريد ان اعرف
if there is anything I can do to help.
إذا كان هناك أي شيء يمكنني القيام به للمساعدة.
No need.
لا حاجة.
We have Tang to help with the clinic.
لدينا تانغ للمساعدة في العيادة.
Everything will be fine.
كل شي سيصبح على مايرام.
Selling medicines online is a good idea,
بيع الأدوية عبر الإنترنت فكرة جيدة ،
but it's not a long-term solution.
لكنه ليس حلاً طويل الأمد.
I asked my boss for help.
طلبت المساعدة من رئيسي.
He can get an interest-free loan for the clinic.
يمكنه الحصول على قرض بدون فوائد للعيادة.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I'll go to the bank for a loan.
سأذهب إلى البنك للحصول على قرض.
I appreciate
أنا أقدر
your kindness.
لطفك.
How about this?
وماذا عن هذا؟
I put the contract here.
أضع العقد هنا.
(Xincheng Group Loan and Security Contract) If you need anything,
(عقد الضمان والقرض لمجموعة Xincheng) إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء ،
call me anytime.
اتصل بي في اي وقت.
I'm leaving first, Mr. Tang.
سأرحل أولاً ، السيد تانغ.
(Xincheng Group Loan and Security Contract)
(عقد الضمان والقرض لمجموعة Xincheng)
There are no more snakes.
لا يوجد المزيد من الثعابين.
Put me down.
انزلني.
Let's go there
فلنذهب إلى هناك
and enjoy the nice scenery.
واستمتع بالمناظر الجميلة.
We're not here to have fun,
نحن لسنا هنا للاستمتاع ،
but to break the spell.
ولكن لكسر التعويذة.
Hurry up.
عجلوا.
Fine.
بخير.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Are you okay?
هل انت بخير؟
My leg.
ساقي.
Did you sprain your leg?
هل التواء ساقك؟
Take a rest over there.
خذ قسطا من الراحة هناك.
Does it really hurt?
هل يؤلم حقا؟
Sit there.
إجلس هنا.
Let me see.
دعني أرى.
Slowly.
ببطء.
Here?
هنا؟
Yes.
نعم.
On the left.
على اليسار.
Okay.
تمام.
On the right.
على اليمين.
This is the same spot as before.
هذا هو نفس المكان كما كان من قبل.
A little further down.
أبعد قليلا.
To the left.
إلى اليسار.
Where is it?
أين هي؟
A little further down.
أبعد قليلا.
But
ولكن
left...
اليسار...
Stop pretending.
كف عن التظاهر.
I won't buy it.
لن أشتريه.
Do you think this is funny?
هل تظن ان هذا مضحك؟
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Don't be angry, okay?
لا تغضب ، اتفقنا؟
Rest for a while.
استرح لبعض الوقت.
Whatever.
ايا كان.
Do you have any plans
هل لديك أي خطط
after breaking the spell?
بعد كسر التعويذة؟
I have a lot of plans.
لدي الكثير من الخطط.
I want to further my studies,
أريد أن أواصل دراستي ،
go to the playground
اذهب الى الملعب
and travel around the world.
والسفر حول العالم.
I can go wherever I want
يمكنني الذهاب حيثما أريد
without a tag-along.
بدون علامة على طول.
Then I'm not part of
إذن فأنا لست جزءًا من
your plan.
خطتك.
Why should I?
لماذا يجب علي؟
Qizi.
بنت.
Qi.
تشى.
(Monastery Gate)
(بوابة الدير)
Is Master Bo Yi here?
هل السيد بو يي هنا؟
I need to see him urgently.
أنا بحاجة لرؤيته على وجه السرعة.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Master is waiting for you.
السيد ينتظرك.
This way.
من هنا.
Is this Master Bo Yi?
هل هذا السيد بو يي؟
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض